Sorry to call you out so suddenly.
You're really popular, Nagase-san,
and I was certain there was someone you liked.
But then I heard you didn't give anyone chocolate on Valentine's Day...
So...
U-Um, I...
I've liked you for a while and—
Just stop.
Huh?
Just stop. I don't want to hear it.
Why not?
Do you hate me or something?
No, I don't hate you.
Then why are you acting so different from usual?
You're usually so bright and cheerful.
Everyone loves you.
You're almost like a ray of light.
I see.
So you like that kind of me too.
You don't like this kind of me, right?
Well... I...
You don't know the real me.
Need I say more?
No, this isn't it either.
I just can't do it.
It's hopeless. Futile. Impossible.
I'm a liar.
No, I haven't lied.
I haven't. Not even once.
And yet...
My ideal and my real are drifting further apart.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't be my normal self.
I heard you rejected Shiroyama-kun pretty hard.
I did.
How can you say that with a straight face?
I bet you think you're hot shit.
You just act like a good girl all the time.
You're the conceited one here.
Huh?
Who asks me out and who I turn down is none of your business.
You've got a really shitty attitude.
If you ask me, you're the one with the bad attitude.
What is wrong with you?!
Why does it have to be you?!
When I... When I...
I...
When you... what?
Bitch.
Hey, did you hear?
Nagase-san rejected him!
I can't believe Iori would say something that mean.
But it's true.
She's so fake.
She just acts like she's nice.
Hey, Iori...
There's a weird rumor about you going around...
I know it's just a lie, though.
You wouldn't do something like that.
I'm sure they're just making things up.
Let them say whatever they want.
Just leave them be.
Y-Yeah. I guess it's only natural that you'd be upset.
I'm not upset at all.
That's it. I've had enough.
Come on, Iori. You're scaring me!
I'm kind of like that.
Okay. I'll talk to you later, then.
Sorry.
Nagase is more bright and cheerful than this.
You probably think I'm a liar.
We're starting our research today.
We don't have much time until the presentation, so we'd better make today count.
Yeah.
You've been acting pretty weird lately, Nagase.
You can't fool me.
Um...
If this has to do with when you turned me down, you don't need to worry.
Sorry.
I mean, you are worried about something, right?
I may not be able to do much,
but if you need me, I'm here for you.
Thank you. I mean it.
I don't need your help!
Just mind your own business!
Well, that's how it is.
Let's split up for the time being.
Maybe we should just disband
the Cultural Research Club.
Thanks for calling me.
This place is too fancy for me to come in alone.
I see what you mean. The place
looks like it was meant for couples.
Anyway, having people know things I don't
want them to is a huge pain in the ass.
Sorry.
It's not like it's your fault.
That's just how it works.
Inaba, what did you mean when you thought that? You really want to disband the club?
It's been on my mind for a while now.
Balloon Vine thinks of us five as a set.
He keeps starting these phenomena to
observe our reactions with that in mind.
I just thought that if we weren't a set
anymore, he'd stop with the phenomena.
So we'd disband to make him leave us alone...
We have no guarantee that he would, though.
Iori's been acting so strange lately.
It's starting to affect the entire class.
If we let this continue, her reputation's going to get even worse.
And...
You're saying that if we separate
ourselves, the phenomenon will stop,
and that would be good for Nagase.
But would you really be okay with that, Inaba?
Yeah, yeah, fine!
I want the five of us to stay together, too.
I don't really want us to disband.
I knew it.
When'd you learn how to read people?
I feel the same way you do.
I want us to always be together.
No matter what stands in our way.
I only got to know you guys because of the CRC,
and I want to keep doing stuff with you guys.
That means you, too, Inaba.
Could you say that last part again?
That means you, too, Inaba?
No, like you did before, with emotion!
That means you, too, Inaba!
Let's put the topic of disbanding aside.
Either way, Iori's in a bad spot.
I'd like to think that she'll be back to her usual self if we give her time, but...
I feel like I didn't really know who Nagase was.
Same here.
Before all this, I was under the impression that I knew her better than anyone else did.
If I hadn't come between you guys, and you started going steady,
maybe Iori wouldn't have changed like that.
I don't think that's true.
I didn't understand how
Nagase felt in the first place.
She would've rejected me whether you came between us or not.
It's not your fault, Inaba.
It's my fault that I got rejected.
What's up?
I got rejected!
What the hell? What's gotten into you?
I got rejected! I got rejected!
I got rejected!
All right!
What the hell are you doing?
I wanted to put the experience behind me, so I shouted it.
I didn't want to keep dragging it around.
I needed to face it, accept it, think about it, and move forward.
You're actually kind of cool...
for someone who got rejected.
You got rejected.
You didn't need to repeat yourself.
What did you want to talk about, Onii-chan?
Have a seat.
Why are you trying to act all grown-up?
It doesn't suit you.
Why are you sitting next to me?
You were supposed to sit across from me.
It doesn't matter.
I have stuff I need to do, so make this quick, okay?
You gave me chocolate on Valentine's Day, right?
Yeah, I did.
When you gave it to me, you said that it was your true love chocolate.
Oh, yeah, I probably did.
So what?
"So what?"
What I'm trying to say is, I love you, but only as your older brother.
We're siblings, and it's not morally sound to—
Onii-chan, you're so funny!
Of course I don't love you like that!
You're just my brother!
R-Right.
No, I mean, I knew that, but I just wanted to make sure, just in case.
Oh, Onii-chan.
You must really care about me.
Well, yeah. We are siblings.
Onii-chan, come closer.
Just so you know,
that was my first kiss.
A kiss on the cheek from my little sister?! Hell yeah!
Ew.
Do we have to play soccer?
It's freezing out here. This is gonna be torture.
I wish I were you, Yui.
You're so good at sports.
So? I'm still going to feel just as cold as you guys.
Iori...
Don't talk to me.
Something wrong, Yui?
Iori's always been there for me.
When I was so depressed that I couldn't even go to school,
Iori visited me at home every day.
Iori is friendly, cheerful, and reliable.
She's a wonderful person.
But she's in so much pain right now.
The emotions she transmits tell me so.
But I don't know what's
causing her to feel that way.
I can feel what she feels, but I
can't understand her as a friend.
I feel the same pain as her, but I can't help her.
When I shut myself in my room,
did they feel the same way I do now?
But just thinking about it won't solve the problem.
We should just do everything we can for our presentation
and when Iori is ready to come back to us.
An obscure café that's perfect for dates,
a Chinese restaurant that's easy on the wallet and gives tons of food,
and a store that sells lots of cute accessories...
We really found a bunch of neat places.
But turning our research into pamphlets and handing them out might be a bit too much.
We're wasting too much time.
We won't beat the jazz band unless we do this.
Are you sure about doing the lettering for the title like this?
Yeah.
If we settle for less and lose, we'll regret it.
And I hate losing!
Yui, you've got the best hand-eye coordination here.
Get your head in the game,
or we're never going to finish.
Oh, sorry.
I just got the feeling that Iori was outside.
She isn't coming today either, is she?
Well, she's got a lot to think about.
We don't know whose thoughts are
going to pop into our heads or when.
It's understandable.
But either way—
I'm scared!
I'm so scared!
Did something happen?
Were someone's emotions transmitted?
Yeah.
You don't need to tell them, Yui.
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, Iori-chan knows we're here for her if she needs us!
We'll just have to wait for her to come to us!
Yeah.
That's what I like about you.
Yes!
Finally!
Yui expressed her love for me!
No!
I only complimented a single aspect of your person!
Don't make such a big deal out of it!
Wh-What happened?
I think I know.
But you're right, Aoki.
We need to do everything we can now, including Nagase's part.
I'm going to go look for Iori.
Th-That was sudden.
Why?
I have to talk to her.
I'll finish off whatever I have left tomorrow, so let me go.
What are you going to do?
Do you need my help?
I'll be fine by myself.
Inaba's biting the bullet, too.
So I need to get a hold of myself as well!
I don't think you should confront her yet.
I agree.
We just said we'd wait for her to come back.
Acting on impulse isn't a good idea.
Don't worry!
And you're the last person I want to hear that from.
I've got a feeling this is going to end poorly.
Not for Iori, but for you.
Trust me, it'll be fine.
I've gotten a lot stronger.
Sorry. I hope I'm not interrupting anything.
We did this before, didn't we?
Except it was me in your shoes.
Yeah.
You saved me back then.
And now it's my turn to save you.
What do you think about this whole emotion transmission thing?
What do you mean?
Like, is it hard on you?
Are you suffering?
It's hard on me, I guess.
C-Could you elaborate?
I want to do whatever I can to help, Iori.
I don't think there's anything you can do.
What's gotten into you, Iori?
You're usually smiling more than anyone else and always trying to make everyone happy.
But you haven't been smiling at all lately.
You've saved me so many times.
I'd do anything to get you back to your normal self! I—
Can't you give this "back to normal" crap a rest?
You don't see it.
You don't get it.
And it's not just you.
It's everyone.
No one sees the real me.
What do you mean?
I'm tired.
It's over. I just can't do it anymore.
Nothing's over yet!
You can do anything you set your mind to!
I can't be friends with Yui anymore.
I love you, Iori. That will never change.
Regardless of how much I change?
Of course.
Even if everything about me changes?
Yeah.
Then what part of me do
you want to be friends with?
If everything about me changes, it won't be me anymore.
I may as well be someone else.
But we still have all the things we've done together.
So, as long as you have a past together,
no matter how terrible a person becomes,
even if they turn into a vicious criminal, they're still your friend?
The person's feelings and nature don't matter to you?
Um...
You're not the Iori we knew!
That's why I can't be friends with Yui anymore.
So your friend turned evil?
No, that's going too far.
She's just being really negative right now.
So you got anxious and called me.
Yeah.
I was hoping a third party would be able to give me some good advice.
I'd like to help, but I don't know the
nitty-gritty of it all, so I can't say much.
Don't tell me you're still
relying on others for everything.
She sure told me.
Hello, and good afternoon, Kiriyama-san.
Oh, the sun is down. Good evening.
Ah, I shouldn't try to use these greetings.
What's wrong, Kiriyama-san?
You look rather nervous.
What do you want?
Ah, please don't get violent.
I'm much stronger than you.
Oh, I see.
You were already aware of that.
What do you want from me?
Kiriyama-san, what do you think of this phenomenon?
Are you scared?
Every part of you is exposed.
Every bit of your heart.
Save me!
Yui, where are you?!
Where are you?!
Good! It reached them!
They'll save me!
Aoki and Taichi will definitely come save me!
...you're still relying on others for everything.
What is it?
I'm scared of this emotion
transmission thing. I hate it.
But I won't run away anymore.
I've made a fool of myself in front of my friends for long enough.
They can know everything
about me. I'm fine with that.
But I'm not just going to rely on them.
They're trying their best to deal with this,
so I need to try my best, too!
I shouldn't be asking my friends to save me.
I shouldn't be trying to deal
with this on my own, either.
We need to get through this, together!
Maybe doing it this way was a bad idea.
I'm tired of it now. Maybe I should stop.
Nothing I say will have any effect.
What are you talking about?
You've become very strong, Kiriyama-san.
You may be even less interesting than Aoki-san.
But maybe that's exactly
what makes this interesting.
No, never mind.
Good-bye.
Good-bye...
Kiriyama!
So you're first, Taichi?
Y-You okay, Kiriyama?
Yeah. Sorry to make you run all this way.
I'm fine.
He's gone.
I see. That's good.
Taichi, I messed up.
What do you mean?
The talk with Iori didn't go well.
I might have even made
things more difficult for her.
You wouldn't be the first of us.
Nagase doesn't even want to see me anymore.
That's not true at all.
I know Iori's just waiting for you to save her.
Taichi, you've gone completely soft!
You used to thrust yourself into people's problems so hard!
Seriously, how could you just sit by and
watch Iori get herself into this situation?
Believe me, I want to do something for Nagase, too.
But I don't know what Nagase wants.
I completely messed up.
What should I do?
You're so wishy-washy!
Would you just man up already?!
I'm clueless about what to do, too!
I gave it everything I had, only to make things even worse!
If you mess up, think about how to not mess up the next time!
Um, Kiriyama, could you calm down?
I mean, I know I've got no right to be lecturing anyone about this,
but you're being so freaking useless that I had to say something!
Don't you ever make me do this again, you idiot!
I-I'm sorry.
You think I'll let you off easy after a little apology?
You think that's all you need to do?
Though I guess I will forgive you.
Th-Thanks?
Is that what I'm supposed to say?
Hey, Kiriyama.
What?
Let's get through this together.
Yeah. Together.
Yui! I'm almost there!
It always takes him way too long!
Or maybe Taichi's just too good at this?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Today's been horrible since it started.
I broke my favorite hairclip,
I got into a fight with my mom,
I overslept,
and I'm not feeling well.
But the thing about life is that something always happens on days like today.
Cut the crap and tell us what you want.
This has gone on for long enough.
What do you want me to do?
Tell us what you want from the bottom of your heart.
You already know, thanks to this emotion transmission thing.
That only tells us bits and pieces! It doesn't tell us everything!
I want to hear everything straight from your mouth!
Why do I have to tell you everything, Inaban?
Iori, you saved me.
I want to save you, too.
I sound pushy, I know.
But we're friends.
Friends help each other out.
So ask us for help already!
Don't force your ideals on me.
What the hell has gotten into you?
You're not acting like yourself at all.
Something really is wrong with you!
You've been like this ever
since you rejected Taichi!
I know you're tired of this
emotion transmission thing,
but tell me...
Why'd you have to turn Taichi down?
I don't understand!
You love Taichi—
Quit forcing them on me!
You wanted to know what's in my heart?
Fine.
You'll get to hear it from my own mouth.
You're just way too selfish.
I don't understand you.
You kept trying to force Taichi and me to start dating.
Day in and day out, it was just,
"You two should go out already!"
And when I finally feel like going out with him,
you get between us and say you love him too.
But when I said that I wouldn't go out with him, you got angry.
What the hell? What do you want from me?
How selfish can you be?
You fan up my feelings, only to come in after, get in my way, and screw everything up.
Now isn't that mean?
Have you ever thought about how I feel?
I should be asking you what you're thinking.
You will cry!
You will scream!
I loved Nagase.
Hard work's something that really shows.
...if all five of us can do the presentation together.
...why you had to make it your fault?!
I don't deserve to feel what they feel.